

# **NGUYEN VAN A**

#### **MARKETING MANAGER**

Male

May 19, 1992

Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and e itself, because it is pleasure, but becaus of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

#### **EDUCATION**



#### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. voluptas assumenda est, omnis dolor repellendus. Temporibus autem quibusdam et aut officiis de administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

#### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. corporate administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

#### **EXPERIENCE**



Sep 2007 - Present

#### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

#### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult olved over the years, sometimes by accident, sometimes on and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

#### Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

#### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

#### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and
- Assist to nska Türkçe Україн goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

**ACTIVITIES** 



Sep 2003 - 2007

#### **CVPRO JSC**

#### Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer egularly and would like to help keep the site on the Internet, please consider donatin' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2004

# HONORS & AWARDS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2013 - 2014

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US which letters occur in English, which is why at a glance it looks pretty real." As Cic

## **REFERENCES**



#### **NGUYEN VAN BINH**

director of cvpro jsc

## **SKILLS**





### **INTERESTS**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt when the then-understood Latin wa and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities